Okay, for the transaction is not a big deal, but yeah, you can keep them like, okay,
total transaction of the month and total transaction of the day.
At the same time, please check the dashboard and see if everything is like in line with the updated
informations.
For example, the net revenue between the gross revenue and expenses, you did an updated.
So every time we push updates to the dashboard, you check the entire dashboard and
you see if the information in the dashboard are the current one that we find out with
the new adjustments and with the new things that we decide.
So don't wait for me to tell you, please, can you update this in the dashboard is still
the same like before or can you please update that in the dashboard is like same like before.
No, you voluntarily check every time the dashboard is everything in the dashboard is updated.