Okay, I'll update everything into the dashboard, remember that every time we adjust something
or we update something, I want you to also reflect the updates into the dashboard.
At the moment, when I see in the dashboard, you put the recipes a bit like confusion
and then when I click on the recipes tab, it gives us like 40 or 40 error.
So you should put like the recipes organized in the recipes tab and already show the cross
check between recipes, ingredients, quantity, expenses we don't about beverage and
food cost from the excel of the expenses compared to the items that we sold.
So you can say at the moment, you can actually find out that the moment would be the stock
of the items that we still have left that we should sell.
Show me this here and update it in the dashboard.